{
    "subject": "resource/Argentina",
    "predicate": "ontology/currency",
    "object": "resource/Argentine_peso",
    "human_readable": "The currency of Argentina is Argentine peso.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9839972257614136,
            "question": "Is the Argentine peso the official currency of Argentina?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9539532661437988,
            "question": "Which country uses the Argentine peso as its currency?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8658351898193359,
            "question": "What is the currency of Argentina?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7557620406150818,
            "question": "How does the value of the Argentine peso compare to other major currencies?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7064580917358398,
            "question": "What is the name of the Argentine peso?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5670651197433472,
            "question": "What is the symbol for the Argentine peso?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4467993974685669,
            "question": "How is the Argentine peso abbreviated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3683001697063446,
            "question": "What are some of the challenges facing the Argentine peso in recent years?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2811081111431122,
            "question": "When was the Argentine peso first introduced?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2227565050125122,
            "question": "Has the Argentine peso undergone any major changes or revisions throughout history?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The currency of Argentina is Argentine peso.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9116_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When was the Argentine peso first introduced?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9116_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some of the challenges facing the Argentine peso in recent years?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9116_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How is the Argentine peso abbreviated?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9116_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9116_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9116_102.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9116_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9116_114.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9116_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9116_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9116_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9116_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9116_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9116_86.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here's the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple, as all the files mention that the official currency of Argentina is indeed the Argentine Peso (ARS)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that the official currency of Argentina is the Argentine Peso (ARS), supporting the given statement."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}